# 肥瘦（肉）都可以吃吧
Can we eat fatty and fat less pork?
# 嗯 吃
yes
# （剁肉声）
Sound of chopping pork
# 起个大早来买肉夹馍
We get up very early to buy pork buns
# 没想到有这么多人 比我还早
I didn’t expect there were so many people are here before me
# 这边的肉夹馍卖的比较便宜
Their pork buns are cheaper
# 上次我买的时候
Other restaurant’s is four or five yuan each
# 别人家都是四五块钱一个
When I bought pork buns for last time
# 他这边时候两块五
There is two and half yuan each
# 不知道这么长时间过去 这边的价格怎么样
I don’t know how much it is now after that long time
# 咱们去看看吧
Lets see
# 顾客排队中
Customers are in lining
# 我要3个标准（肥瘦）的肉夹馍
I want to buy 3 regular (both fatty and fatless pork) pork buns
# 盐味一般
Medium salty
# 不要辣椒
No spicy pepper
# 看这一锅肉 真的是饿了
I am starving when I saw meat in the pot
# 好香啊 还是熟悉的味道
Smells very fragment with familiar flavor
# 咱们买了3个脆皮肉夹馍 5元一个
We bought 3 crunchy pork buns, 5 yuan each
# 这次呢 我要的是标准（肥瘦）的
I ordered regular (both fatty and fatless pork this time
# 有点肥肉带点皮
A little fatty with pork skin
# 吃起来口感没有那么干
With less dry texture
# 因为猪肉涨价了嘛 肉夹馍的价格也跟着涨了
The price of pork buns increased because price of pork increased
# 不过这边的生意还是很好的
Their business still very good
# 以前吃的肉夹馍 一般都是腊汁肉夹馍
We used to eat
# 这次咱们买的是潼关肉夹馍
# 它们最大的区别在于这个饼
The biggest differences between them are the bun
# 我先咽一下口水
Let me swallow my saliva first
# 烧饼外面是非常酥脆的
Shaobing are very crispy on the outside
# 呈现这种螺旋花纹的状态
Shows the state of spiral pattern
# 刚出炉的肉夹馍 真是迫不及待地想咬一口
I can't wait to bite the freshly baked pork buns
# 太酥脆了 所以很容易掉渣
Its easy to fall off dross of bun
# 饼就像千层饼 油酥饼一样
The bun is like thousand layers of buns and shortbread
# 层呢 就是一层层的
With multiple layers
# 这么一碰 饼皮都会掉下来 特别的酥脆
Its very crispy
# 肉夹馍 一口下去 不仅能够吃到烧饼的酥脆
U can feel crispy crunch of buns with one bite
# 还有肉的咸香
And salty fragment of pork
# 两种味道在唇齿之间交融 在打架
Two flavors are fighting in your lips and teeth
# 仿佛都在宣示 我最好吃
As it declare I’m the delicious
# 以前吃肉夹馍觉得肉很重要
I used to think pork is very important when I eat pork bun before
# 这次发现 饼也很好吃
But now I find out the bun is delicious too
# 有的时候 这个饼的酥脆甚至可以掩盖一下肉的油腻
The crispy of buns even cover up the greasiness of the meat sometimes
# 顾客：我看我9点来拿馍
Customer: I will take my buns at 9am
# 你9点来拿 我给你留着 馍还热乎
You can come at 9, and I will keep the buns warm for you
# 你要瘦的还是肥的（肉）
Do you want fatty or fatless pork?
# 有点肥也行
It’s okay to have a little fatty
# 刷油（为了）分层
Brushing oil for layering
# 小姐姐 我问一下 这一个饼皮大约多重
Sis how heavy for the curst?
# 这是多少 得120g
About 120 grams
# 2两多点
emmmmmmmmmmmmm
# 两个人擀饼皮 确实要比煎和烤烧饼更快
Two people roll out the crust are faster than to fry and bake
# 所以 饼皮都是整齐地摞放一起
So crusts are stacked neatly
# 待会阿姨就是一个个把它们放在烤箱里
Aunt will put them into oven one by one later
# 油酥（油和面混合制成）
“Yousu”(mixed with oil and wheat)
# 烤制（进烤箱）
Bake(into oven)
# 有那个坏的饼吗
Do you have bad baked buns
# 刚才一个大哥来买肉夹馍
A guy come to buy pork buns
# 但是他不是来买烤好的饼
But he is not coming for well baked buns
# 他是说 这边有没有烤的不好的饼
He is asking if we have bad baked buns
# 就是比较便宜地能够买回去
So that he can buy with cheaper price
# 饼都是很好的 但是有时候火候不到位
Our buns are good, but sometimes not bake well
# 这样的饼吃起来没有做得好的饼口感那么好
So it taste not as good as well baked buns
# 第二盆肉登场
Second pot of meat coming
# 顾客：我要4个加蛋的
I want four pork buns with eggs
# 吃瘦的还是稍微带点肥的
Fatty or fatless pork?
# 肥瘦的吧
Both of them
# 肥瘦搭配
Fatty and fatless
# （剁肉声）
Sound of chopping pork